[
  {
    "id": "622",
    "theme": "Frontend",
    "result": [
      [30, "you should learn more"],
      [60, "very good, but you should repeat some topics"],
      [90, "excellent"]
    ],
    "list": [
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "What does HTML mean",
        "answers": ["HyperText Markup Language", "HeadingText Markup Language", "HyperText Mode Language", "HeadingText Markup Language"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which tag is used for links",
        "answers": ["<a>", "<link>", "<p>", "<button>"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Where should you place the <title> tag?",
        "answers": ["head", "main", "body", "footer"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which link is absolute?",
        "answers": ["http://www.site.com/page.html", "/page.html", "./page.html", "page.html"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which tag is used for images?",
        "answers": ["img", "image", "picture", "figure"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Can you place incline elements into block elements?",
        "answers": ["yes", "no, it's not semantic", "yes, but you should be careful", "no, it's not valid"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "How many times you can use ID on a page?",
        "answers": ["One", "Two", "There is no limit", "There is no attribute ID"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which tags are used for lists?",
        "answers": ["dl", "ol", "ul", "rl"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "How to make element flex?",
        "answers": ["display: flex", "<flex>", "class=\"flex\"", "flex: 1"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Choose values for justify-content",
        "answers": ["space-around", "space-between", "space-evenly", "space-revert"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which default value is in align-items?",
        "answers": ["stretch", "initial", "center", "space-around"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Can you use flex and grid in the same website?",
        "answers": ["yes", "no", "yes, but on diffent pages", "no, it will ruin the layout"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Can grid element be a grid container?",
        "answers": ["yes", "no, it will ruin the layout", "yes, but only inline-grid", "no, it's not valid"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "How to define an array in JavaScript?",
        "answers": ["[]", "new Array()", "Array()", "array()"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which statement returns a value",
        "answers": ["return", "break", "throw", "catch"]

      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "What does DOM mean",
        "answers": ["Document Object Model", "Document Objects Mode", "Digital Optical Modulation", "Digital Optical Modul"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "A method to round a number",
        "answers": ["Math.ceil()", "Math.floor()", "Math.round()", "Math.pow()"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "This method converts a string to an array",
        "answers": ["split()", "slice()", "charAt()", "splice()"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "What will return parseInt('007')",
        "answers": ["7", "'007'", "error", "nothing"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "How to add element elem in the array array?",
        "answers": ["array.push(elem)", "array.shift(elem)", "array[array.length] = elem", "array.pop(elem)"],
        "correct": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "57135",
    "theme": "JavaScript",
    "result": [
      [30, "you should learn more"],
      [60, "very good, but you should repeat some topics"],
      [90, "excellent"]
    ],
    "list": [
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "How to define an array in JavaScript?",
        "answers": ["[]", "new Array()", "Array()", "array()"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which statement returns a value",
        "answers": ["return", "break", "throw", "catch"]

      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "What does DOM mean",
        "answers": ["Document Object Model", "Document Objects Mode", "Digital Optical Modulation", "Digital Optical Modul"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "A method to round a number",
        "answers": ["Math.ceil()", "Math.floor()", "Math.round()", "Math.pow()"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "This method converts a string to an array",
        "answers": ["split()", "slice()", "charAt()", "splice()"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "What will return parseInt('007')",
        "answers": ["7", "'007'", "error", "nothing"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "How to add element elem in the array array?",
        "answers": ["array.push(elem)", "array.shift(elem)", "array[array.length] = elem", "array.pop(elem)"],
        "correct": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "89345",
    "theme": "HTML",
    "result": [
      [30, "you should learn more"],
      [60, "very good, but you should repeat some topics"],
      [90, "excellent"]
    ],
    "list": [
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "What does HTML mean",
        "answers": ["HyperText Markup Language", "HeadingText Markup Language", "HyperText Mode Language", "HeadingText Markup Language"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which tag is used for links",
        "answers": ["<a>", "<link>", "<p>", "<button>"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Where should you place the <title> tag?",
        "answers": ["head", "main", "body", "footer"],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which link is absolute?",
        "answers": ["http://www.site.com/page.html", "/page.html", "./page.html", "page.html"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which tag is used for images?",
        "answers": ["img", "image", "picture", "figure"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Can you place incline elements into block elements?",
        "answers": ["yes", "no, it's not semantic", "yes, but you should be careful", "no, it's not valid"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "How many times you can use ID on a page?",
        "answers": ["Один", "Два", "Сколько угодно", "Не одного, нет такого атрибута"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Which tags are used for lists?",
        "answers": ["dl", "ol", "ul", "rl"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "How to make element flex?",
        "answers": ["display: flex", "<flex>", "class=\"flex\"", "flex: 1"]
      },
      {
        "type": "checkbox",
        "question": "Choose values for justify-content",
        "answers": ["space-around", "space-between", "space-evenly", "space-revert"],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Which default value is in align-items?",
        "answers": ["stretch", "initial", "center", "space-around"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Can you use flex and grid in the same website?",
        "answers": ["yes", "no", "yes, but on diffent pages", "no, it will ruin the layout"]
      },
      {
        "type": "radio",
        "question": "Can grid element be a grid container?",
        "answers": ["yes", "no, it will ruin the layout", "yes, but only inline-grid", "no, it's not valid"]
      }
    ]
  }
]